Hello, everyone, today we're going to give you
a review of the IDBI Small Cap Fund Direct Growth.
If you're looking for a small-cap
fund, we're creating a series
on the small-cap category, which is listed
in the link description. We've already
made videos, including some smaller ones.
You should definitely watch this video. There are a few
more options.
If you're a investor and can wait at least four to five
years, you should invest in this type of
fund. We
also believe that if you're an investor,
you should keep the location of at least two of your phones.
Before subscribing, I want to tell you something.
My name is Ajit Singh Rawat, a
certified financial advisor, and I've been
associated with the industry for the past 12 years.
On this channel, we
share regular information regarding regular investments.
If you want to keep yourself updated,
please subscribe.
First, let's talk about some basic details. The
fund house is IDBI Mutual Fund.
It's an open-ended scheme.  And its start
is 21 June 2017, the benchmark Nifty Small
Cap is 250 RS, which means
water management
subscribe
expression is
higher Angry Birds
exit load is top, if you withdraw before this then you
can subscribe and with minimum
₹5000, if we talk about it in February
2016, then in this one year it has
given a return of around 8.30, whereas it has
given an annual return of 28.12 and subscribe question, if
you had invested in this fund a year ago, then
today its value would have been more than the
fund,
if you had invested in this fund three years ago, then if we
talk about 90, then in equity
9808005005 has been
invested, whereas in midcap and
smallcap only one investment has been made,
11.37, the total number of subscribe
buttons
is more, whereas in the category
from point of view, their competitors are happier,
their average is 48.50,
portfolio turnover  Ratios indicate
how frequently fund managers change their interests,
which is
34%. Talking about option holdings,
LG Equipments Ltd.
holds 4.33%, Investment Grade Will
Not Unlimited holds 4.25%, Sainik
Investment Industries Ltd. holds
around 3.7%,
Construction Ltd. holds 3.6%,
Investment of India Ltd.
holds around 3.13%, and when the
fundamentals of the top ten holdings were checked, it was
found to be in a very good position,
like Dhadak Ke Inaar Construction Ltd.
Its promoting holding is 51.40%.
Promoting holding indicates
how much trust the owners of that company have in that company. So,
here the promoting holding is
also quite good. Sales Produce Company has
around 10% and
32.90% and
23.22% and the debt on this company is also very
low at Rs.
20 crore. Some companies are in a very good
position, which can give good returns.  If we
talk about fund managers then subscribe 8010603 more, then this point is made by
Mishra Alok Ranjan ji,
who is managing 233 schemes and I manage
this for Rs 64 crores. If we
talk about vacancies then this standard
deviation is around 24.71 when the cricket category
Everest 24.3 i.e. Five Little Champs
Audition tells how much risk
and wall tile one has, then if this value is
less than 2000 then it is considered good,
but according to Everest it shows
how good returns any request gives, which is
0.80
9806 at
05035 position, it tells us that
whatever return we had estimated, it is
called that which is very low.
Like the physical review of IDBI Small Cap Direct Fund Growth. If you liked the video then
we keep bringing such school information, so
please like and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you.  You for
watching a